{
    "subject": "resource/Sigrid_Undset",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfDeath",
    "object": "1949-06-10",
    "human_readable": "Sigrid Undset died on June 10, 1949.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8938843607902527,
            "question": "When did Sigrid Undset die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6029399037361145,
            "question": "In what year was Sigrid Undset born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5743840336799622,
            "question": "Which country was Sigrid Undset from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.532248854637146,
            "question": "Was Sigrid Undset a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5028989911079407,
            "question": "Where did Sigrid Undset live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49058642983436584,
            "question": "What is Sigrid Undset known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37623751163482666,
            "question": "Is there a specific historical period that Sigrid Undset's works often depict?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3071539103984833,
            "question": "Did Sigrid Undset win any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24853847920894623,
            "question": "What genre of literature did Sigrid Undset write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2428586483001709,
            "question": "What are some of Sigrid Undset's most famous works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sigrid Undset died on June 10, 1949.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2617_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of literature did Sigrid Undset write?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2617_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Sigrid Undset win any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2617_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a specific historical period that Sigrid Undset's works often depict?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2617_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2617_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Sigrid Undset died on June 10, 1949\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because multiple documents (78.txt, 31.txt, 29.txt, and 33.txt) confirm that Sigrid Undset died on June 10, 1949."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Sigrid Undset died on June 10, 1949."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}